Don't look at me like that.
Help me find it.
There it is!
That's right.
It's him.
We can use him.
I'll go find Ju.
Captain!
Search the whole village.
No one was found.
Nothing suspicious either.
Nothing?
Yes.
Keep searching the mountain.
Don't miss anything suspicious.
Search the mountain.
Miss Ye.
Interpreter Luo.
I'm here to get the medicine for the commander.
What a coincidence.
to meet you here.
Are you waiting for someone?
Colonel Takemici.
Colonel is so lucky.
to have a woman like you.
Ju.
Ying.
You're finally off work.
What's up?
Let's talk somewhere else.
Okay.
Tell me.
What's the matter?
This afternoon,
that Japanese bullied you.
and worried about you.
So I came to see you.
It happens all the time.
That Japanese soldier is a coward.
He's holding his breath.
You can only vent it with me.
The world is tough now.
You've been wronged
working in the Japanese army hospital.
I have to be bullied by them all day.
If I don't do this job,
I might end up like Hye Hye.
Still, you can't let others slaughter you.
We need a goal in life.
I have a goal.
Do you know
who I live for?
For whom?
I said
Don't laugh at me.
Brother Dragonfly.
Shameless.
You always want to be my sister-in-law.
You promised not to laugh at me.
Just kidding.
In my heart,
you are my sister-in-law.
Brother Dragonfly.
is the only hope
for me to live.
My brother is so lucky.
Ju.
Have you ever thought
Without the Japanese,
Now,
you and my brother
really married.
and my sister-in-law.
Of course I want to.
I think about it every day.
every day.
I just hope the Japanese
get out of Sanbu Island.
Ju.
Let me ask you.
This afternoon
the second-class soldier
Is it
who harmed Huihui?
is him.
That bastard.
You took care of him.
But your brother told me every day
to kill him.
I was so scared.
He deserves to die.
Ju.
I need your help.
I also have an injured soldier here.
He has a fracture.
He has a fever.
Takemici and I have a plan.
to switch him with your wounded soldier.
to take care of him.
I'm a doctor.
I'll tell you what to do.
You're a doctor.
What about Takemichi?
Who are you?
Ju.
No matter what we do,
you have to trust me.
We're not bad people.
We won't do anything bad.
Only you can help me with this.
Bik-ying.
This is too big.
If the Japanese find out,
they will be executed.
Ju.
You always think the hospital is your shelter.
It can protect you.
However,
[Even heaven is hell]
even heaven is hell.
This is
to me,
to anyone,
to anyone.
Is the injured soldier
Is he the American
looking for?
So you came to the island
to save him.
Why should we risk our lives
to save an American?
We're fighting
with the Americans.
We must stop the Japanese
and slave the whole world.
Where is that American now?
Somewhere safe.
Ju.
Don't be afraid.
As long as you have faith,
as long as you have faith,
you'll have courage.
You can do it.
I'm not like you.
I'm not a brave person.
I wasn't.
But as long as I have faith,
people will grow.
This is too big.
Let me think about it.
Okay?
Okay.
But don't
about this.
Okay.
I won't let dad know.
Tell me when you've made up your mind.
Okay.
Yuichi Suzuki.
Yes.
Hurry up.
Colonel.
Yuichi Suzuki.
Last February,
[the private jet General Taikok took]
Before the bee incident,
before the accident.
for daily maintenance and maintenance.
At that time,
you were on duty.
right?
Yes.
I need to ask you something.
I'll ask.
You answer.
What time was it?
at that day?
Colonel.
Last February,
It's been too long.
I don't remember the exact time.
Take your time.
But you have to remember
when did you switch shifts?
Who was there?
or who touched the plane,
you have to make it clear to me.
Captain.
We found a cave on the mountain.
This way.
Where?
We're almost there.
This way.
Captain.
Thank you.
Salute.
Captain.
Is it the American who skydiving?
It can't be wrong.
Block this area quickly.
Yes, sir.
Get another team to back us up.
Okay, I'll be right there.
What are you looking for?
A car came here.
A car?
Find out what happened at the base yesterday.
Yes.
There was no mission yesterday.
Did our colonel
came here too?
In that case,
we won't be able to find anything.
I don’t want to suspect Colonel.
But the evidence
point to him.
Should we take action on him?
There are more than ten cars like this in the base.
How can we prove
the wheel track belongs to him?
Captain.
Captain!
Team 4 is here!
Team 4 was ordered to arrive.
We have 36 people.
Thirty-one.
There are five missing. Why?
Airport Defence's high-shot squadron
We sent a car to pick up five people.
The investigator from Tokyo.
who came from Tokyo?
I think so.
Irigami.
You stay here and organize the investigation.
I'm going to the airport guard.
Don't you need more people?
No.
I'm leaving.
My brother is here.
I'll get him for you.
No need.
I'll get it for you.
No.
Stop calling you brother.
What?
Ju is outside.
Go.
Ju.
What is it?
Ju will have to take care of the Major.
Tell her.
Go.
Okay.
Xia.
Where are you going?
Dad.
I'll be right back.
Excuse me.
What are you two mumbling about?
Nothing.
Is Ju outside?
About the Major,
I need Ju'er's help.
I'll ask my brother to tell her.
If it weren’t for this war,
Xia and Ju would have been married.
Maybe
even hold his grandson.
Okay.
Hurry!
Captain Oshima
What do you want from my soldiers?
Colonel, you need to know
Last year,
in the last year.
That was
the Defense Brigade and the Special Forces Police Brigade
Each team will pick one member
to be on duty.
I think so.
All participants
who participated in
must be questioned.
Captain Oshima.
Are you looking for me?
I always want to arrange a time
to invite you to dinner.
Go ahead.
I'll pick another time.
Sorry.
I've been busy these days.
I forgot about it.
Like this.
Today...
I'll finish work early today.
Let's get together tonight.
Tonight then.
Deal.
Akino-san!
Oshima-san's treat tonight.
Come with me.
It's an honor.
Ta-da.
By the way,
Check.
I checked the staff and list.
Among the people on duty that day,
Why is one missing today?
Let me check.
Check.
Someone is missing.
I see.
Check.
The defence team is missing.
Private Leiji.
Where is he?
A few days ago, he went out to look for a girl.
but the villagers broke his bones.
He's lying in
in the hospital.
Check.
Okay.
Put this person at the end.
Yes.
Bye.
Get back to work.
Okay.
See you tonight.
Call the next person.
What do you think about
what do you think?
Ju.
Don't be afraid.
No one will force you
to do things you don't want to do.
I'm scared.
I just want to live
with you.
I'm not as brave as you.
And I'm afraid...
I'm afraid
will be more cruel.
Their cruelty
has never changed.
Brother Dragonfly.
Tell me.
what will happen
after they die?
I don't know.
I never thought about it.
How can I not?
Something scary.
I never wanted to.
No matter what,
what will come will come.
You'll be scared too.
I'm not afraid if I were myself.
But sometimes,
I think of my dad
and Ying Er.
and you,
I'm really scared.
I made you laugh at me.
I heard from the elders in the village
people become stars after they die.
If someone misses him
If you see a star
it means those who miss him are thinking about him.
Is that so?
Ju.
In the sky of Sanbu Island,
is sad.
Japanese should die.
When the Japanese really leave,
our Sankanma...
No.
The whole country is free.
we can
be together for real.
forever.
Jimmy.
You should leave now.
Good luck, guys.
Sir.
I beg you.
arrange a plane for me today.
I can't stay any longer.
Listen.
All British
have collapsed in Myanmar.
That's hell.
You're going to die if you leave now.
Where is the plane you promised me?
In the past week,
I didn't see any plane.
Do you know why?
Major.
They're looking for
the route to China,
was destroyed.
This route is located
a mountain in Nanlu
It's like a mountain in the back of a camel.
The top of the sea
is over 8,000 meters.
The whole route
Gosan Snow Peak
Canyon Ice River.
The average height
over six kilometers.
And the flying height
can only reach
can only reach 5 km.
In other words,
you can only fly in the valley.
Only two of the six planes
only two flew to China.
Four fell
[was destroyed in China.]
Major.
That's why
you didn't see
last week.
I have a plane.
I can help you.
But I have to warn you.
This is very dangerous.
I know.
I'm willing to take the risk.
This is a suicide flight.
Major.
I hope you're not the second Wilt Chen.
Sir.
I can't wait any longer.
Take me to the coordination room.
Lu Hang, 347.
Keep the height of 3,524.
3407 got it.
Turn right.
Height 3,05 meters.
No.
The mountain on the left.
Up to 6,500 meters.
There's a mountain on the right.
Charlie.
Pull him up.
Oh my god.
No.
Charlie.
Pull him up.
The second believer.
[fell off the plane]
fell off the plane and died.
Please do your best in the Chinese war zone.
to rescue the believers
who was trapped in the Japanese base.
and sent him to Qizhou Airport
on April 18.
Captain.
I heard.
The body was stolen?
What's going on?
Hello?
What's going on over there?
We searched
the Mount Hutang.
Nothing new.
Tell them to go back and rest.
Inform all leaders to have a meeting.
Dismiss.
The day before yesterday,
the North of the base was attacked.
Another smuggling case occurred at night.
During the investigation,
Captain Irikami found
on the shore.
[We found the footprints on the plane]
we found the American hiding place
on the plane.
In Tan Jiawan this afternoon,
the body of the stowaway
was stolen by the people again.
Why are we so passive?
Did the headquarters ask about the progress?
Commander Fujita is very angry about this.
He asked me to solve the case
within a week.
Anyway,
all signs indicate that
the cave we searched today
is where the Americans are hiding.
We were too late.
We focus
to the beach and Tan Jia Wan Village.
We've been thinking
what went wrong.
A stranger landed on the island.
Without the help of the locals,
without the help of the locals?
Sasaki is right.
Where is this American
hiding now?
A sentry has gone missing.
I think
he found out by chance.
This American...
was killed by him.
The body was buried somewhere.
What should we do next?
I want to know what you think.
Tell me.
If we catch this American,
everything will be clear.
I can feel
I can catch him soon.
There are too many things
on the island these days.
How dare they take the body?
This is the first time
on the island.
The Macau triad
for two or three years.
This time, I suddenly came back.
It doesn't look like an independent case.
Maybe he came to pick up this American.
I think so too.
The popularity of Chinese on the island
is growing.
When the bodies were taken away by them,
the situation was almost out of control.
It seems that keeping these scoundrels
is a disaster.
I think there must be something
must have something to do with the islanders.
Commander Fujita.
I always believe that kind of benevolent policy
I think we should
all of them.
Kill them all.
I know what to do.
You should use your brain more.
Who is behind all this?
How did they contact outside the island?
On the isolated island
on such a tight island,
except pigeons,
no one can escape.
Pigeon.
Did you see the pigeon?
Last morning,
the man who was sent to Mount Hugtang said
I saw a pigeon
I think I saw a pigeon.
Are you sure it's a pigeon?
The guards said it looks like
Did you see where it came from?
No.
He disappeared in the blink of an eye.
Pigeon.
Captain.
Are you suspecting someone on the island
using pigeons to communicate with the outside world?
We have been suspecting that
there was a communication in the village.
If it was a pigeon,
Of course.
The person who keeps the pigeon
is the biggest suspect.
Wait.
The clues of pigeons are very important.
Keep it a secret.
so that we can capture them.
Dismiss.
Dismissed.
Have a seat.
Sasaki.
Listen.
I need you to make
a secret operation plan.
We plan to lift the sea ban on April 12.
The expulsion period is five days.
Special Forces Police Brigade
will organize all young men on the island
to the sea.
Save it for fishing.
Li Juhai.
Sit on the sea.
A tiger goes to the sea to catch a tiger.
The reason is
The Day is coming.
The entire island
To celebrate the Emperor's birthday,
lift the sea ban.
Remove the sea ban?
This will bring a lot of trouble.
The gangsters in Macau
will also
to contact these people on the sea.
is using them as bait.
It's best to write in the plan.
Yes, sir.
and give some information to Macao.
and hide
in Macau,
and those who often make trouble on the island.
Macau gangsters.
I'm going to
all at once.
Do you mean the sea?
Check a list of people
on the island.
All young men on the island
must be on this list.
Understood.
Now,
there are only the old, weak and children left on the island.
Then it'll be peaceful.
Indeed.
I want to see it too.
Sasaki.
Write a report yourself.
to the commander.
Just report to the others.
Don't leave any trace.
Understood.
Irigami.
Stay here. I have something to tell you.
I’ve arranged something tonight.
to invite Colonel.
Come with me.
Are you going to declare war against Colonel?
We are soldiers.
Soldiers can't go against their superiors.
Yes.
But...
my intuition tells me he's suspicious.
I believe in this instinct.
If you want to declare war,
you have to declare war with a smile.
Smile.
Let's go.
Come here.
Go to Fukuda Ping Chuan now.
Tell him to leave the best private seats
in the tavern.
Tell him
I'm going to invite
a distinguished guest.
Tell him to prepare more sake.
and bring a few women with good looks.
Yes.
Telecom.
Record it.
The one who called
Mr. Rongze.
Yes.
The garrison team
Two Macau smugglers were killed.
According to preliminary investigation,
both smugglers belong to...
an organization called Anlan Hall in Macau.
The purpose of smuggling to the island is unknown.
Please cooperate with the investigation.
Find out
in Macau.
The point is Anlan Clinic, Area 8 in Macau.
Please pay special attention to these people.
the contact information
of the Sansa Island.
This mission must be carried out secretly.
Yes.
I've been so busy lately.
Thank you.
I'm always confused.
The chief of Macau Special Class
of Macau Special Class.
We were classmates.
Later, we had our own duties.
Please ask him for help this time.
That's a good idea.
Get ready to go.
The show is about to start.
You need to smile.
Just smile?
That Colonel Takemichi
is from the palace.
have seen the world.
What is this?
A confession.
Suppressant?
This thing
in the battle.
The intelligence bureau police and the search bureau
It's often used.
Will his life be in danger?
No.
He will only
reveal all his secrets.
And they keep nagging.
You keep nagging.
Pour this into the wine today.
Remember.
pour it into the third cup.
The third glass.
I see.
Good evening.
Captain Oshima.
I've been waiting for you.
Please.
Thank you.
I've prepared the best wine today.
As you like.
My pleasure.
Captain Oshima.
The Commander said
you don't like drinking
nor women.
But why
buy me a drink today?
The commander just told you
I don’t like drinking.
but he didn't tell you.
I can drink a lot, right?
Cheers.
Cheers!
Colonel.
Yes.
I can't help reminding you.
your Chinese woman
is unreliable.
We Japanese women are reliable.
Cheers!
Come on.
Commissioner Shen.
Let's have a toast.
Thank you.
Sorry.
I
have thought it through.
I have to tell you.
the island and I
have connections.
A pigeon.
right?
Last night,
two of my men went back to Sankanma.
Today,
the island replied to me.
What happened?
They're all dead.
Where are they?
They're fine.
Only my two brothers died.
Maybe they are the people
you're looking for.
They're fine.
Fortunately,
my nephew and my niece are fine too.
Gosh.
I was so worried.
Colonel is from the palace.
Put it nicely.
Make it thinner.
Slightly.
It's too big.
Let me do it.
Line up properly.
Actors.
Oshima Hao Wood Dragon (Japan)
Wei, Chen, Shao, Tong,
Luo Zhiyong, Liao Wangwang.
Sasaki, Middle Spring Hero (Japan)
Commander Fujita, Kobayashi Chengnan (Japan)
Dr. Jin. Ouyang Wangjia.
Halong, Chen Weixu.
Akashi, Songpo.
Rat Zhao Shuai.
Yumiko Liu Yi.
Inabe Akira Senbo (Japan)
Stupid Ho Zhi Long.
Lieutenant Li, Zhang Zhizhong.
Yau Gang Wang Zheng.
[Yohei Matsukaku]
Shoichi Kimura
Yamamoto 56, Kenichi Miura (Japan)
Leiji Jiang Kun
Mr. Chen, Luo Shiping.
Chen, An, Gao Haishan.
Director Wang, Chen Xuming.
Commissioner Yan, Huang Wenhao.
Li Jingfeng from Chenqiao.
Bingyi, Yue Junling.
Captain Zhong, Zhou Jie.
Da Hu, Zhang Jun.
Tiger Jin Guangzheng.
Yuan and Ma Yan.
Master Qin, Zhao Haiying.
Cigarette girl Yu Li
Qing, Mu, Liu Fenggu.
Ye, Tian, Feng, Falls.
Yang Cheng Ming from Nagano.
Secretary Zhao, Shi Yifu.
Zheng Cai Fu, Chen Jun.
Xu Shengsheng, Xue Conghai, Zhang Xiaolei, Xiao Zhenyang, Li, Yu, Liu Haibo, Zhu Chao Qun.
Yang Xiaomei Jingjing, Yin Xin, Xie Lei, Ding Yongyan, Zuo Longqiang.
Zhang Menglian, Liang Xiaoxia, Li Jinxiao, Wang Jingru. Ding Zhiyuan, Dong Xiaoya, Zhang Tengyun.
He Guiling, Liu Youlin, Li Jiawei, Auspicious. Yin Zhifei, Jia Shuyi, Zhang Haifeng,
Vice director Ma Yunbo Zhang Yiyi
Vice-director, Wei Tianci.
Assistant editor Zhai Kai.
Photographer, Gao, Wei.
Lighter Wang Gujun
Recording instructor, Lim Xin.
Team leader, Guo Baojun.
Liu Shusen, deputy team leader.
The team leader, Wang Qitao.
Ma Yulong.
Vice-captain of props, Liu Junqing.
Production Deputy Director Yu Haitao
to lead Su Kewen
Liang Ting Hui.
[Sun Tianyong]
Drama Producer Yang Haiqun Zhu
Legal consultant, Sun Shouheng.
Translator Qian Lei, Luo Yu E.
script planner, Wu Tian.
Manager Wang Kang Ning.
pilot Lauson Sky. Hart.
Pilot C-46, Geffon. David Blue.
Charles Michelle Demson. Aldride.
Japanese commander, Teishi. Mizuno.
Spanis Jeff. Respector.
Marshal. Watson.
I'm a Japanese officer, Takasaki YAM.
Alexander, Ko Sia, Kevin. Joy.
Colonel Kubo P.J.Marino America.
Preparation pilot Kuri Aron. Wilton.
Staff table.
Director assistant Luis. Feeling Delgado.
The drama Cherry Su
The martial arts team
The martial arts director, Liu Jie.
Actor assistant director Go Haesan
Photographer Lee Moon Ho.
Recording assistant Liu Xingxing Cao Mengchao
Lee Seong-ha.
Hwan-ha.
Music editor Dai Tingting Liu Zongyun
Music Producer Kun Music Studio
Recorder John Kurrander.
Music coordination Zhang Xiaoming and Qiu Yunbing
Theme Song: "The Moon Open Eyes".
How bright the performance is.
Recording/mix Tong Xinyu
Producer Liu Jingjing Liu Xuandou
Producer Liu Jing Yang Yu
Lyrics: Zhao Jun, Zhang Jingyi
Composition/Arrangement Wang Tianjin
Late production.
Peking Pei Hua Culture Co., Ltd.
Project Manager Wang Yiwei.
Environmental Effect Editor Wang Ke Yu Jiang Ji Yu Lau.
Special Effect Editor Wang Yangbing Wang Hawk
Full-range recording, Wang, go.
Color Li Yang.
Narrator white horse.
Japanese voice tutor Qian Lei
Voice actor Takahashi Ching-hwi
Video Director, list Jia.
Video director Liu Bing
The leader of the model team, Fan Haowei.
Lu Haowei.
Documentary.
Chief Editor, Mjurlei.
Li Siying.
Legend Paradise on the Hai of Guangjiang, Guangjiang, Guangzhou and Guangzhou.
Guangzhou’s Tourism Center
Guangdong Kaiping Ping Building Tourism Development Co., Ltd.
Guangzhou Shawan Ancient Town Tourism Development Co., Ltd.
Zhongshan Film and TV City Co., Ltd.
New film and television Project Studio.
Beijing Huixin Yijie Movie Planning Co., Ltd.
Costume sponsor = Jiangsu Qianyu Environmental Engineering Co., Ltd.